<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:56:06 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Investing</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:56:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/curriculum/</guid>
      <description>Book List The intelligent investor Principles of Economics Software Engineering at Google: Lessons Learned from Programming Over Time Warren Buffett Accounting Book: Reading Financial Statements for Value Investing Algorithmic Trading: Winning Strategies and Their Rationale Mostly Harmless Econometrics: An Empiricist&amp;rsquo;s Companion An Introduction to Quantitative Finance The Outer Limits of Reason: What Science, Mathematics, and Logic Cannot Tell Us The Theory That Would Not Die: How Bayes&amp;rsquo; Rule Cracked the Enigma Code, Hunted Down Russian Submarines, and Emerged Triumphant from Two Centuries of Controversy Web Scraping with Python: Collecting More Data from the Modern Web Python for Data Analysis: Data Wrangling with pandas, NumPy, and Jupyter Python for Finance Cookbook: Over 80 powerful recipes for effective financial data analysis, 2nd Edition Technical Analysis of the Financial Markets: A Comprehensive Guide to Trading Methods and Applications some basic math when needed some basic ai when needed Month 1: Foundation and Fundamentals DONE Week 1: Basic Financial Concepts Learning Objective: Introduction to the world of finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmic trading</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:55:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/main/</guid>
      <description>Hypothesis I&amp;rsquo;m not sure this will work.
this might work, because
market might be efficient but people are not rational General Strategy need not perfect information nor perfect algorithm
I&amp;rsquo;ll perform the trading manually and see if I can automate some of my work.
Goal money beat the stock market by a noticable magine
when stock market yields 5% return, I want to achieve 5.5% return (10% relatively) study ai, finance, decision making</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>decisions</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:44:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/decision/</guid>
      <description>process select buy candidates
for each candidate
indicators produce (multiple) predictions prepare buy / sell (2nd level indicator)
combine multiple predictions on each candidate (weight them)
produce possible buy candidates
evaluate current holdings
for each holding, 2nd level indicator evaluate holding
We have bought this holding with this prediction data Is the prediction still valid? can you (indicator) evaluate the current standing?
decide buy / sell
With new candidates for buy, evaluations for current holdings</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
